Broadcasting Christmas is a tv movie, romance,
drama film directed by Peter Sullivan.
When the opportunity to co-host a talk show with the fabulous talk show diva Veronika
presents itself two weeks before Christmas, Emily thinks this is her big break.
To her surprise, she discovers she has stiff competition with Charlie, the
local TV anchor who is her near equal on another station.
With such interest and support for both reporters, a contest is created: for the two weeks leading up to
Christmas, who can cover the best and most meaningful Christmas stories on the local news?
Emily Morgan, played by Melissa Joan Hart.
Charlie Fisher, played by Dean Cain.
Patrice Montgomery, played by Cynthia Gibb.
Veronika Daniels, played by Jackée Harry.
Stanley Morgan, played by Richard Kline.
Abby, played by Krista Braun.
A Christmas Carol is a 1984 Christmas fantasy television film adapted
from Charles Dickens' novella A Christmas Carol (1843).
The film was directed by Clive Donner, who was an editor of
the 1951 film Scrooge, and stars George C.
Scott as Ebenezer Scrooge.
It also features Frank Finlay as Marley's Ghost, David
Warner as Bob Cratchit, Susannah York as Mrs.
Cratchit, Angela Pleasence as the Ghost of Christmas Past, Edward Woodward as the Ghost of Christmas Present and Roger Rees as
Scrooge's nephew Fred; Rees also narrates portions of Charles Dickens' words at the beginning and end of the film.
It was filmed in the historic medieval county town of Shrewsbury in Shropshire.
The film has received significantly positive reviews, with general praise going to the sets, soundtrack, cinematography, and the performances of the
cast, particularly Scott's portrayal of Scrooge, with many critics and reviewers considering it one of the best adaptions of the novel.
The film explores themes of rivalry, tv news anchor, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.